Finding aid for the Bonnie Cashin Collection of Fashion, Theater, and Film Costume Design LSC.0440
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Bonnie Cashin Notebooks, 1949 - 1995; 15 oversize boxes
  - Address Books, undated, mid - late 20th century; 9 volumes and 2 rolodexes
    - Address book., undated, mid - late 20th century; 1 volume (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Address book., undated, mid - late 20th century; 1 volume (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Address book., undated, mid - late 20th century; 1 volume (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Address book., undated, mid - late 20th century; 1 volume (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Rolodex., ca. 1970 - 2000; 1 rolodex (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Rolodex., ca. 1970 - 2000; 1 rolodex (Box 156, Folder 2)
- Personal Papers, 1937 - 2000; 40 oversize boxes (323 folders)
  This series contains personal correspondence and materials collected by Bonnie Cashin. The series is particularly rich in documenting Cashin's museum holdings, participation in the International Design Conference in Aspen, travel, and creation of the Innovative Design Fund. The series also includes clippings files of subjects of interest to Cashin as well as personal letters. The series is subdivided by topic: Misc. museum events; non-fashion, Museum / school donations; holdings and exhibitions of Cashin designs; Cashin signatures and logo designs; Nasa; International Design Conference in Aspen; clippings and documents regarding travel; correspondence with friends and associates; color; collected editorial material regarding fashion; collected editorial material, non-fashion; collected poems and essays; collected art; humanitarian causes; inventions of interest; documents and correspondence re. Buckminster Fuller; Innovative Design Fund; recorded and transcribed interviews with Cashin. All writings by and recordings of Bonnie Cashin contained in this series are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
  - Recorded and Transcribed Interviews with Cashin (Personal Papers), ca. 1970 - 1987
    This subseries contains audio cassette recordings and written transcripts of interviews with Bonnie Cashin. The audio cassettes have been transferred to CD. All original recordings of Bonnie Cashin contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Cassette recording: Belmont Freeman's birdcages. Tape 1 of 2., ca. 1984-1986; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 33)
    - Cassette recording: Belmont Freeman's birdcages. Tape 2 of 2., ca. 1984-1986; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 34)
    - Cassette recording: Martin Skalsky's chair., ca. 1985-1987; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 35)
    - Cassette recording: Kent Bailey's prototype lamp. Tape 2 of 2., ca. 1983-1985; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 36)
    - Cassette recording: Kent Bailey's prototype lamp. Tape 1 of 2., ca. 1983-1985; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 37)
    - Cassette recording: Todd Siler's light screen., ca. 1982-1983; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 38)
    - Cassette recording: Joel Sokolov. Tape 1 of 2., ca. 1984-1985; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 39)
    - Cassette recording: Joel Sokolov. Tape 2 of 2., ca. 1984-1985; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 40)
    - CD: Joel Sokolov. CD 1 of 2., ca. 1984-1985; 1 CD (Box 241, Folder 41)
    - CD: Joel Sokolov. CD 2 of 2., ca. 1984-1985; 1 CD (Box 241, Folder 42)
    - Cassette recording: "Answering Machine / Cooper Union"; reader copy on CD., ca. 1970s; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 15)
    - Cassette recording: "BC talking: innovative thinking; Innovative Design Fund initiative; state of design"; reader copy on CD., ca. 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 26)
    - Cassette recording: "SI: the Art Show / Bonnie Cashin" tape 1 of 2; reader copy on CD., October 17, 1984; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 27)
    - Cassette recording: "SI: the Art Show: Bonnie Cashin" tape 2 of 2, reader copy on CD., October 18, 1984; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 28)
    - Cassette recording: "saga of the New York telephone"; reader copy on CD., ca. 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 29)
    - Cassette recording: "Cashin messages: incoming"; reader copy on CD., ca. 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 30)
    - Cassette recording: "Bonnie Cashin: Beginner Music Class" from Mary Chapin; reader copy on CD., ca. 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 31)
    - CD:"Bastille Day Luncheon with references to Bucky Fuller.", 1979; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 40)
    - CD:"Bucky Fuller.", ca. 1979; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 41)
    - CD:"Answering Machine / Cooper Union.", ca. 1970s; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 45)
    - CD: "Lugging sweaters for WWD photo session; Tina's impression of Lesley Nonkin.", May 7, 1980; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 57)
    - CD: "BC talking: innovative thinking: Innovative design fund initiative; state of design.", ca. 1980; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 58)
    - CD: "The Art Shoe / Bonnie Cashin"; 1 of 2., October 17, 1984; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 59)
    - CD: "the Art Show / Bonnie Cashin"; 2 of 2., October 17, 1984; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 60)
    - CD: "Saga of the New York Telephone.", ca. 1980; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 61)
    - CD: "Cashin Messages: incoming.", ca. 1980; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 62)
    - CD: "Beginner's class music / Bonnie Cashin" from Mary Chapin, 1 of 2., ca. 1980; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 63)
    - CD: "Beginner's class music: Bonnie Cashin" from Mary Chapin, 2 of 2., ca. 1980; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 64)
  - Clippings and Documents Regarding Travel (Personal Papers), ca. 1952 - 1995; 38 folders
    This subseries contains documentation of Bonnie Cashin's travels. The subseries primarily consists of clippings and brochures regarding locations visited as well as personal contacts and receipts. Some materials contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - National Geographic maps collected by Cashin., 1959 - 1964; 15 maps (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Letter regarding Cashin's suitcase stolen on route from Milan to Venice, including list of stolen clothing., August 2, 1951; 2 pages (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to Spain., ca. 1952; 13 pages (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to Russia., 1959; 64 pages; 3 booklets; 2 brochures (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to Dubrovnik, Yugoslavia., July 1975; 38 pages; 3 booklets; 6 brochures; 3 maps (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to England and Paris., 1977; 15 pages; 10 booklets; 2 brochures; 1 map (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to Portugal and London, 1979; 21 pages; 1 brochure; 1 map (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to Sante Fe, New Mexico., October 1983; 20 pages; 3 booklets (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to Europe (London - Hamburg - Cologne - Baden-Baden - Paris)., 1983; 22 pages; 4 booklets; 12 brochures + 6 maps (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to London., 1984; 9 pages; 3 brochures (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's Red Sea Passage, a tour with the Metropolitan Museum of Art., 1984 - 1985; 32 pages; 1 booklet; 1 map (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to Canada - Seattle., 1987; 26 pages; 1 booklet; 1 brochure (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to London., 1988; 1 page; 2 booklets (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's "Danube River Adventure.", 1988; 34 pages; 4 booklets; 8 brochures + 3 maps (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to Hamburg - London., 1989; 5 pages; 1 booklet; 1 map (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's Northeast Passage, a tour with the Metropolitan Museum of Art., 1991; 3 pages; 1 booklet; 1 brochure (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to London., 1994; 17 pages (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's Smithsonian tour to Spain, Morocco, Canary Islands, Senegal, and Brazil., 1994 - 1995; 24 pages; 2 brochures (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's trip to England., 1996; 7 pages; 4 brochures; 1 booklet; folder (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding Cashin's Seabourne cruise., 1996; 8 pages; 8 brochures (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Envelope sent to Cashin from India., 1957; 1 envelope (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Reprint of poster advertising emigration to California., ca. 1960s; 1 poster (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - Cashin Signatures and Logo Designs (Personal Papers), ca. 1950 - 1985; 3 folders
    - Slides of Cashin's signatures., ca. 1980; 2 slides (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Museum Events; Non-Fashion (Personal Papers), October 15, 1969 - 1984; 4 folders
    This subseries contains ephemera from museum projects collected by Bonnie Cashin.
    - Slides; American Crafts Museum Competition entries., 1984; 12 slides (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Audio reel: "Sound" audio exhibit from the Museum of Contemporary Crafts., October 25, 1969 - January 4, 1970; 1 audio reel (Box 239, Folder 11)
    - CD: "Sound" exhibition, Museum of Contemporary Crafts., October 25, 1969 - January 4, 1970; 1 CD (Box 239, Folder 22)
  - Nasa, ca. 1970s - 2000; 4 folders
    This subseries contains documents and slides regarding Nasa missions collected by Bonnie Cashin.
    - Slides; Nasa collection titled "Our Universe.", undated, Ca. 1970s; 40 slides (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Documents regarding Nasa., October 1, 1976; 21 pages (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding planetary exploration., ca. 1970s - 2000; 7 pages; 1 booklet (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Viking and Voyager missions., ca. 1970s; 64 pages; 2 booklets (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - International Design Conference in Aspen, June 1975 - 1987; 3 oversize boxes and 1 folder
    This subseries contains Bonnie Cashin's collection of conference publications and recordings of lectures from the International Design Conference in Aspen which she attended between 1975 and 1987.
    - "The Future Begins Today" conference publication; in conjunction with Saks 5th Avenue., ca. June 1975 - 1976; 1 booklet; 1 folder; 32 pages (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - "Exploring Change" conference publication., June 13 - 18, 1976; 1 booklet; 8 pages (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - "Shop Talk" conference publication., June 12 - 17, 1977; 1 booklet; 1 page (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - "Japan" conference publication., June 17 - 22, 1979; 1 booklet; 1 poster (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - "Form and Purpose" conference publication., June 15 - 20, 1980; 1 booklet; 9 pages (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - "The Italian Idea" conference publication., June 14 - 19, 1981; 3 booklets; 1 page (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - "The Future Isn't What it Used to Be" conference publication., June 12 - 17, 1983; 2 booklets; 12 pages (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - "Neighbors: Canada, Mexico and the U.S." conference publication., June 17 - 22, 1984; 1 booklet (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - "Illusion vs. Truth: Perception as the Basis for Design" conference publication., June 16 - 21, 1985; 1 booklet (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - "Insight and Outlook: Views of British Design" conference publication., June 15 - 20, 1986; 1 booklet (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - "Failure / Success" conference publication., June 14 - 19, 1987; 1 booklet; 11 pages (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Cassette recording: Tom Wolfe at "Exploring Change" conference, 1976; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Cassette recording:Brendan Gill at "Exploring Change" conference., 1976; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Cassette recording: Ian McHarg at "Exploring Change" conference., 1987; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Cassette recording: Duccio Turin at "Exploring Change" conference., 1987; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 4)
    - Cassette recording: Raymond Sokolov at "Exploring Change" conference., 1976; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 5)
    - Cassette recording: Saul Bass at "Shop Talk" conference., 1977; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - Cassette recording: Jack Roberts and Lou Dorfsman at "Shop Talk" conference; tape 1 of 2., 1977; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - Cassette recording: Jack Roberts and Lou Dorfsman at "Shop Talk" conference; tape 2 of 2., 1977; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 8)
    - Cassette recording: George Nelson at "Shop Talk" conference., 1977; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 9)
    - Cassette recording: Ettore Sottsass at "Shop Talk" conference., 1977; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 10)
    - Cassette recording: Ivan Chermayoff at "Shop Talk" conference., 1977; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 11)
    - Cassette recording: Julian Beinart at "Shop Talk" conference., 1977; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 12)
    - Cassette recording: Moshe Safdie at "Shop Talk" conference., 1977; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 13)
    - Cassette recording: "Applied Design" talk at "Japan in Aspen" conference., 1979; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 14)
    - Cassette recording: "The Synthesis of Contradiction" talk at "Japan in Aspen" conference., 1979; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 15)
    - Cassette recording: Buckminster Fuller at "Form and Purpose" conference; tape 1 of 2., 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 16)
    - Cassette recording: Buckminster Fuller at "Form and Purpose" conference; tape 2 of 2., 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 17)
    - Cassette recording: Donald Micheal talk "Future responsive Governance" at "Form and Purpose" conference., 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 18)
    - Cassette recording: Paul MacCready talk "Human Powered Aircraft" at "Form and Purpose" conference., 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 19)
    - Cassette recording: Oliver Selfridge at "Form and Purpose" conference., 1980; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 20)
    - Cassette recording: Sergio Pininfarina talk "An Industrialist in the Land of Machiavelli; A Tough Job" at "The Italian Idea" conference., 1981; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 21)
    - Cassette recording: architectural panel discussion at "The Italian Idea" Conference; tape 1 of 2., 1981; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 22)
    - Cassette recording: architectural panel discussion at "The Italian Idea" Conference; tape 2 of 2., 1981; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 23)
    - Cassette recording: Cashin and Jack Lenor Larsen presenting "I.D. Fund Seminar" at "The Future Isn't What It Used To Be" conference., 1983; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 26)
    - Cassette recording: I.F. Clarke talk "Patterns of Expectation" at "The Future Isn't What It Used To Be" conference., June 13, 1983; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 27)
    - Cassette recording: C. Hampden-Turner talk "New Paradigms for Excellence: Process, Pattern ad Improvisation" at "The Future Isn't What It Used To Be" conference., 1983; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 28)
    - Cassette recording: "'26 / '86 MIT Reprise: In Memory of Roy Lamson.", 1986; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 29)
    - Cassette recording: "Synergy: Beyond Ideas of Wrongdoing: Arrien" at "Success and Failure" conference., 1987; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 30)
    - Cassette recording: Ralph Caplan., ca. 1980s; 1 audio cassette (Box 241, Folder 31)
    - CD: Cashin and Jack Lenor Larsen presenting "I.D. Fund Seminar" at "The Future Isn't What It Used To Be" conference., 1983; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 56)
  - Museum / School Donations, Holdings and Exhibitions of Cashin Designs (Personal Papers), June 18, 1953 - November 2001; 4 oversize boxes and 6 folders
    This subseries contains documentation of Bonnie Cashin's work collected and exhibited by museums and design schools. The subseries is arranged alphabetically by institution.
    - Requests for donations of Cashin designs to museums., March 12, 1959 - April 29, 1959; 54 pages (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - List of museum donations by Philip Sills., 1979 - 1981; 4 pages (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding the American Museum of the Moving Image (Astoria, New York)., August 28, 1987 - November 25, 1987; 20 pages (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Art Center College of Design (Pasadena, California)., 1978 - 1987; 21 pages (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Papers re. Bard Graduate Center (New York, New York) exhibition "Furnishing Fashion: Material Connections in 20th-Century Design"; Cashin essay "Upholstered for the Evening" by Stephanie Day Iverson., December 2004; 10 pages (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding Baylor University (Waco, Texas)., August 1, 1986; 1 page (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Accessions records of Cashin designs at the Brooklyn Museum of Art (Brooklyn, New York)., 1951 - 1986; 209 pages (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Documents regarding Brooklyn Museum of Art (Brooklyn, New York)., December 12, 1962 - November 23, 1998; 40 pages; 1 booklet; 1 brochure (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Documents regarding Color Association of the United States., October 11, 1993; 5 pages (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Documents regarding Cornell University (Ithaca, New York)., 1980 - 1991; 42 pages (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Documents regarding City University of New York (New York, New York)., Spring / Summer 1987; 6 pages (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Documents regarding Detroit Historical Society (Detroit, Michigan)., August 4, 1986; 1 page (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding Directors Guild of America (Hollywood, California)., January 24, 1977 - February 25, 1977; 4 pages (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Drexel University (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)., January 1976 - May 20, 1988; 73 pages; 1 booklet (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Fashion Institute of Technology (New York, New York)., 1969 - December 13, 1999; 143 pages; 1 brochure (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding Franklin Museum of Science (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)., 1981 - 1985; 3 pages (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding Goldstein Museum of Design, University of Minnesota (St. Paul, Minnesota)., April 5, 1976 - December 16, 1988); 61 pages; 1 booklet; 1 magazine + 124 slides (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Documents regarding Henry Miller Gallery., March 8, 1983; 2 pages (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Documents regarding Honolulu Academy of Arts (Honolulu, Hawaii)., August 9, 1977 - December 1977; 12 pages (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Documents regarding Indiana University of Pennsylvania (Indiana, Pennsylvania)., April 14, 1977 - February 8, 1978; 3 pages (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Document regarding Katonah Gallery (Katonah, New York)., July 7, 1974; 1 page (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Documents regarding Kaufman's Department Store (Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania)., December 13, 1976 - Fall 1977; 22 pages (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Documents regarding Kent State University Museum (Kent, Ohio)., 1995 - 1996; 3 pages (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Documents regarding Los Angeles County Museum of Art (Los Angeles, California)., November 6, 1975 - October 12, 2004; 14 pages (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Documents regarding Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York, New York)., January 1, 1968 - August 16, 1998; 90 pages; 1 folder; 1 magazine (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding Michigan State University (East Lansing, Michigan)., October 20, 1978; 2 pages (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Mint Museum., 1995; 2 pages (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Mount Mary College (Milwaukee, Wisconsin)., February 2, 1970 - January 17, 2001; 138 pages; 2 newsletters (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding Museum of the City of New York (New York, New York)., March 23, 1981 - June 4, 1984; 8 pages (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding specialty store Neiman Marcus (Dallas, Texas)., May 14, 1956 - September 27, 1976; 6 pages; 1 folder (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Documents regarding New York Public Library, Lincoln Center (New York, New York)., August 6, 1986; 8 pages (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Documents regarding New York University., May 20, 1999 - June 11, 1999; 7 pages (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Documents regarding North Carolina School of Science and Mathematics., ca. 1980 - 1982; 10 pages (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Documents regarding Ohio State University (Columbus, Ohio)., July 10, 1980 - March 22, 1994; 50 pages; 1 booklet; 1 slide (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Documents regarding Otis Art Institute (Los Angeles, California)., January 21, 1985; 1 page (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Documents regarding Pace Gallery (New York, New York)., June 8, 1977; 1 page (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Documents regarding Parsons School of Design (New York, New York)., 1980 - 1984; 76 pages (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Documents regarding Philadelphia College of Textiles and Science (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)., February 8, 1988; 1 page (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Documents regarding Philadelphia Museum of Art (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)., January 14, 1961 - May 6, 1998; 56 pages; 2 booklets (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Documents regarding Portland Art Museum (Portland, Oregon)., August 1977 - April 24, 1978; 46 pages (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Documents regarding Pratt Institute (Brooklyn, New York)., 1983 - 1988; 12 pages (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Documents regarding Ray College of Design (Schaumburg, Illinois)., March 9, 1987; 1 page (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Documents regarding Rhode Island School of Design (Providence, Rhode Island)., March 21, 1981 - July 3, 1986; 1 booklet; 14 pages (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Documents regarding Royal Ontario Museum (Toronto, Ontario)., July 16, 1982 - October 22, 1982; 3 pages (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Scovill Apparel Fasteners (New York)., February 6, 1982; 2 pages (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Documents regarding Shippensburg State College (Shippensburg, Pennsylvania)., April 9, 1980 - April 6, 1986; 33 pages (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Documents regarding Smithsonian Institute (Washington, D.C.)., October 2, 1966 - December 7, 1981; 115 pages (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding State Historical Society of Wisconsin (Madison, Wisconsin)., November 27, 1969 - August 5, 1985; 141 pages; 27 polaroid photographs (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Documents regarding Texas Tech University (Lubbock, Texas)., June 15, 1980 - March 6, 1982; 1 booklet; 5 pages (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Documents regarding Time- Life exhibition of Cashin's work (London, England)., November 1966 - March 1967; 25 pages (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Documents regarding University of California, Los Angeles., June 10, 1977 - February 11, 2004 July 18, 1977; 7 pages (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Documents regarding University of Cincinnatti (Cincinnatti, Ohio)., February 13, 1987; 12 pages (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Documents regarding University of Kansas (Lawrence, Kansas)., June 1, 1984 - July 11, 1987; 5 pages (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Documents regarding University of Washington (Seattle, Washington)., May 3, 1976 - April 5, 1991; 18 pages (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Documents regarding University of Wisconsin, Madison., April 23, 1984; 2 pages (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Documents regarding University of Wisconsin, Stout (Menomonie, Wisconsin)., October 19, 1978 - December 4, 1978; 2 pages (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Documents regarding Victoria and Albert Museum (London, England)., June 29, 1971 - December 7, 1971; 5 pages (Box 147, Folder 15)